https://xxxspacegirls.us/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentThis privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for (https://xxxspacegirls.us). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:• See what data we have about you, if any. • Change/correct any data we have about you. • Have us delete any data we have about you. • Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Updates Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 818-745-0940 or via email: wm@lawebprojects.com.Membership StatusYou need to be logged in to be able to subscribe to this blog or purchase any of its posts.Use the link below to login or register.Login   RegisterAffiliate ProgramCheck out our other unique niche sites at AdultWorldMedia.com.
Search for:
SearchWelcome to Xxx Space Girls. In the past the site use to cover mostly the SciFi sex niche with warrior babes and huge cock aliens hunting the space girls and fucking them in group porn orgies. Now I have dedicated Galactic Girls for covering the alien porn niche.
Space Girls has been restructured and here I will post high resolution fantasy image galleries only. No movies! The image galleries will cover all kinds of unique fetish niches like nun sex, scifi sex, fetish porn, babes, glamor, etc. Super high quality photo galleries, magazine style, featuring top porn stars and sexy fashion models. Enjoy!
The Best Unisex Handmade Sissy PantiesFace Masks with Filter PocketCotton reusable cheap double layer washable face mask with filter pocket - Free USA Shipping!Recent Posts Possessed by Demon girl inserts sword in pussy Busty Blonde Warrior drilled by alien sex machine Bondage Art Part 2 Long Legs Blonde Model Licking Her Feet Long Legs teen stripping sissy panties in her first porn shootRecent Commentsnoblejondy on Busty Exotic Girl Fucked in Sci Fi LABCategoriesAimee SweetAlira AstroAmber MichaelsAmyAnastasia PierceAngela MeliniAngela RyanAnna MillsAnna MolinovaAprellaAriaArianna AlyseAriel XAshley ReneeAudraBarbie BlakeBee TranBobbi BarringtonBobbi EdenBrittney SkyCailey TaylorCandaceCaresa MeCarol CrowCocoCrissy CumsCrissy MoranDaisy MarieDaniella RushDanikaDarby O RileyDarenziaDeeDeja DaireDolly DreadfulDomiana DemonicaDru BerrymoreEmily MarilynErotic ArtEstelleGaugeGianna MilanoIsabella CamilleIvy RedJacqueline SummersJade MarcelaJade StarrJana CovaJasmine DJasmine St ClaireJAXTRAWJelena JensenJessica StarJessie SummersJessie VJewell MarceauJoye LaneJudy StarrJulie SimoneJustine SandsKami AndrewsKasorn SwanKenyaKira EggersKirsten PriceKristina MoscowKylie WyldeLaura LaceLea De MaeLea MartiniLeila SwanLexi MathewsLexxi TylerLolaLoni BunnyMadison DahlMaeva ExelMasuimi MaxMelissa AshleyMelissa LaurenMeriah NelsonMia FoxMichelle AstonMichelle MayleneMidoriMika TanMiss ConductMistress PersephoneMonicaMonica SweetheartMoniqueMonique DaneNatalie DemoreNatasha DollingNicholeNika DavitoNikki ArmstrongNoraParis KennedyPoisonRaquel DevineRebecca LinaresRebecca LordRegina HallRhonda LeeRoxanne HillRuby LusterSamantha SterlyngSatine PhoenixSatyQSharon WildShayla SummersShe Devil VixenSienna SunnSilvia SaintSofiaStephanie TrippSWANTaimie HannumTall GoddessTerri SummersTiger LilyTJToonsTyla WynnVega VixenVictoria KnightVictoria SinnZdenka PodkapovaFriendsMuslim Sex Movies - Horror SexBilling SupportPlease visit www.EPOCH.com, our authorized sales agent.Powered by Magic Members Membership Software
